JARED TANKSLEY

PREMIER SERVICE CONSULTANT



CONTACT INFORMATION



405-385-2795



✓ Jared.Tanksley1@gmail.com



10708 Glover River Dr. Yukon, OK 73099



jaredtanksley.github.io/aboutme

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration - Entrepreneurship Oklahoma State University - Stillwater, OK

Minor in Accounting 24 Credit Hours Needed for Bachelor's

Full Stack Web Developer Nanodegree Udacity (September 2021)

ACCOLADES

AP Scholar Fall 2010

Dean's List Fall 2011

Harry and Maxine Weise Scholarship Fall 2012 & 2013

Choctaw Nation Higher Education Scholarship

CERTIFICATIONS

- AT&T Technical Knowledge Test II
- Smith Defensive Driving
- ACT National Career Readiness Gold

ABOUT ME

Detailed oriented, self-motivated, and performance driven individual that adapts to new situations and environments quickly. I enjoy being a leader to my peers and helping others to succeed. Also, I strive to become the expert in every situation, and I'm extremely proficient in computer, networking, and cloud-based technologies as well as Microsoft Office.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Premier Service Consultant

AT&T/Work From Home/July 2021 - Current

- Participate in a sales-driven workplace requiring monthly quotas to be obtained in a highly interactive environment.
- Required to set daily objectives and self-manage in a virtual work from home space.
- Collaborate with peers and customers on troubleshooting mobility technical, billing, and order issues.
- Provide and coach customers based on information from various computer systems to work towards a common resolution as well as relaying new information to help other agents.
- Heavily research detailed promotional or technical information to quickly provide an accurate response or resolution.

Wire Technician

AT&T/Oklahoma City, OK/November 2015 - July 2021

- Test, verify, and repair a broad range of AT&T video services, copper cable internet, and fiber optic internet into a customer premises while providing and communicating information and education.
- · Negotiated various contract modifications, followed-up and explained quotations, revisions, and conditions with customers in a collaborative manner.
- · Handled business invoicing and billing as well as the planning and analysis of the procurement function for materials.
- · Preformed and completed job assignments based on reading data from telecommunication blueprints and orders.
- Assigned as a duty supervisor on the weekend for over a year to coach, mentor, and supervise other technicians and train DirecTV managers on U-Verse management responsibilities.
- Maintained continuous top performance metrics for over five years. Achieved top technician in every major measured category for all of the Oklahoma City metro area in 2018.

Shipping Coordinator/Documentation Specialist 180 Medical/Oklahoma City, OK/December 2014 - November 2015

- Initially worked as a liaison for the shipping warehouse and sales specialist to review, communicate, and distribute important documentation for shipping as well as addressing general shipping and logistics information.
- Promoted within six months to a documentation specialist; named a top performer in accuracy and total amount of document processing first month out of training.
- · Worked with HIPAA privacy laws and utilized Microsoft Word, Access, and Excel on a daily basis as well as internet-based database and informational systems.
- · Consulted with third-party insurance agents to provide accurate insurance information for patents and obtain detailed information to meet patient needs. Verified extremely complex insurance information.